atbcoin.com 2017-09-14

# ATB Privacy policy | ATB Coin - Good for Business. Good for You

Privacy Policy

The present Privacy Policy determines how ATB Coin stores, protects, and uses your personal information collected during the use of the ATB Coin website [https://atbcoin.com](https://atbcoin.com/)

In order to perform the functions of the service associated with the transactions of the User’s cryptocurrency, we can collect personal identification information from users in various forms, including but not limited to user visiting of our site, using site services, filling in forms or chatting with technical support, as well as in other possible ways.

Users can voluntarily, if necessary, tell us their name, e-mail address, information about the used cryptocurrency addresses. These data are not mandatory. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily provide such information to us.

Users can always refuse to provide personal identification information. Most of the personal identification information we collect is required for the assets transactions of the users.

We do not have access to login / password of specialized social media and other resources. If the user leaves feedback about our work through the third-party system we are using, we can not collect any data in the social media profile unless the user gives us the appropriate permissions through the standard social media interface protocol.

Non-personally identifiable information

ATB Coin does not collect non-personally identifiable information about visitors when they interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, the name of the browser, the type of computer or mobile device, and technical information about the means of communication with our site, such as the operating system, phone model, Internet provider, mobile operator and other such information.

Cookies in web browsers.

The site can use cookies and Google Analytics or similar data services. With the help of these data, information on the actions of visitors on the site is collected in order to improve its content, the functionality of the site and, as a result, create high-quality content offering services for visitors. You can change your browser settings at any time so that the browser blocks all cookies or notifies you about sending these files. Note that some functions and services will not work properly.

How we use the collected information

ATB Coin may collect and use the User’s personal information for the following purposes:  
• To perform the services declared by the site. This applies to the addresses of the User’s cryptocurrency transactions.  
• For a personalized call to the User made by Support Service.  
• We can use User feedback to improve our products and services,  
• To process transactions or advice on the use of our service.

How we protect user information

We take appropriate security, administrative, and technical measures to protect any personal data you provide regarding the collection, storage and processing, as well as security measures to protect your accounts against unauthorized access, modification, disclosure or destruction of User’s personal information and transaction data. ATB Coin has a high level of security, thanks to a reliable protocol and cryptography, as well as additional levels of authentication. The declassification of personal data of system participants by hackers is impossible, since attackers will need to attack all computers on the network, which is technically impossible.

Joint use of the User Personal Information  
We do not sell, rent or lease personal data of users to third parties.  
Please note that any transactions on the blockchain network are public and we can not exclude transaction data from the blockchain.

Alterations to Privacy Policy  
ATB Coin has the right, at its discretion, to update the privacy policy at any time. We recommend that users frequently check this page to find any changes and stay informed about how we help protect personal information. By using the site https://atbcoin.com you acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to periodically review the privacy policy page and be aware of the changes.

Your agreement to these terms  
Using this site https://atbcoin.com and the services provided, you express your consent to this privacy policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our website and services. The subsequent use of the site after changes to the privacy policy will also be considered as your acceptance of these changes.

Feedback  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy feel free to contact our online support at your convenience.
